<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="UpdateFeatureBase_GiddyUpCore">
		<modNameReadable>Giddy-up! Core</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>GiddyUpCore</modIdentifier>
		<linkUrl>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=37323.0</linkUrl>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_GiddyUpCore">
		<defName>GiddyUpCore_2_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
All Giddy-up! mods except Giddy-up! Mechanoids have been updated to support Rimworld version 1.1 (including the expansion). Credits for this update go to Sarg Bjornson, who's responsible for a major part of this update. This version also supports Rimworld 1.0, so no need to worry if you're still using that version. 

Giddy-up! Mechanoids will be updated once What the Hack has been updates (which will take some time). 

This update includes the following improvements and fixes: 
- Added more overlays for vanilla animals. These overlays prevent that pawns overlap the heads, horns or other things that animals have. 
- Made sure the name tag of a pawn doesn't overlap the animal's head when an animal is mounted. 
- Fixed null reference errors that the wait for rider job sometimes threw.
- Compatibility with the new HugsLib version. 
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_GiddyUpCore">
		<defName>GiddyUpCore_2_0_3</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.0.3</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
Giddy up has been updated with the following changes!

- Large performance improvement. Your game should run noticably smoother. Giddy-up should barely impact FPS from now on. 
- Added built-in support for the Multiplayer mod (credits go to Cody-Spring)
- Fixed a nasty issue that could occur when you change allowed areas, resulting in pawns getting stuck. 
- Fixed Giddy-up Caravan issue that could result in caravans being overloaded after leaving the map. Credits go to okradonkey for this fix. 
- The potential inventory mass of pawns is substracted from the mass a mounted animal can carry when world travelling. In other words: things a pawn carry no longer get a free ride when riding. 
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_GiddyUpCore">
		<defName>GiddyUpCore_3_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>3.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
All Giddy-up! mods except Giddy-up! Mechanoids have been updated to support Rimworld version 1.2 (with multi-version support for 1.0 and 1.1). Giddy up Mechanoids will be updated once I'm done with the What the Hack update. Enjoy!
Cheers, Roolo
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_GiddyUpCore">
		<defName>GiddyUpCore_3_0_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>3.0.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
Giddy-up Core has been updated. Changes: 
- Improved performance (credits go to Karim for this). 
- Fixed multiplayer mod support (credits go to AriAlavi). Giddy-up is fully compatible with the multiplayer mod again, though with the following known issues: 
    - If using arbiter and battlemounts, firing from a mount will cause a desync
    - NPCs riding animals does not draw for the host, only clients (eventually leading to 
	  desync). Therefore, NPC mounting is automatically disabled in the settings for 
	  multiplayer users by default. 

Thanks go to the testers of this update as well: 
- ubergarm
- Diego75547
- Poj

Cheers, 
Roolo
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
</Defs>